Guide to the Ken Kennedy academic records, 1967-2007 MS 206
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: Committees, 1986-2007 (Boxes 17-39)
  - Subseries B: Non-Rice, 1987-2007
    - LANL CCS DRC Chair Mtg. Handouts. 21 Nov 2002 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - NSF General (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - CISE Advisory Committee - resign (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - GBO Report - Ken's Comments (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Thrall Directors Fees (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Thrall Time Sheets (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Bethlehem Steel Case (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - CISE (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - CSTB - NRC (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - NSF (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - CRAY - 2002 Annual Shareholder Mtg. (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - CRAY rule 10b5-1 Plans. 26 Nov 2002 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - CRAY Board Teleconference. 13 Sept 2001 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - CRAY Board Meeting Teleconference. 1 Aug 2001 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - LANL CCS DRC Summary of Review (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - LANL Science and Technology Assessment, July 2001-June 2002 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - CRAY - Power of Attorney. 18 Oct 2002 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - CRAY - S3 Signature Page. November 2002 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - CRAY Board Packet. 25 June 2001 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - CRAY 2002 Operating Plan (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - CRAY Inc. Form10-K Proxy Statement Revised 2002 Operating Plan (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - CRAY 2002 Salary Recommendations (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - CRAY Inc. Board Consent re: 401k Amendments (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - CRAY Registration Statement (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - DoD Retreat - March 1997 - Rice University (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - CRAY 10-K. 1 April 2002 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - CRAY - Annual Report 2001 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - CRAY Board of Directors Meeting/Teleconference. 5 Feb 2004 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - CRAY Board of Directors Meeting. 29 Oct 2003 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - CRAY Teleconference (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - CRAY Board of Directors Meeting. 21 May 2003 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - CRAY Board of Directors Meeting/Teleconference. 21 May 2003 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - CRAY Board of Directors Meeting. 5 Feb 2003 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - CRAY Compensation Teleconference 2002 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - CRAY Board Meeting. 29 May 2002 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - CRAY Investors Teleconference. 6 March 2002 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - CRAY Board Teleconference. 1 March 2002 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Phone call with Jim Rottsolk (CRAY). 25 Jan 2002 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - CRAY Board Meeting. 7 Nov 2001 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - DoD (Department of Defense) (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - DoD Thank You Letters (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Argonne Machine Purchase (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Argonne General (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - LANL (General) (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Meeting with Pierre Nelson 1999 (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - Intellectual Integration in Theory and Software (Box 22, Folder 46)
    - CISE II Site Visit (Box 22, Folder 47)
    - HPFF Proposal (Box 22, Folder 48)
    - HPFF December 1992 (Box 22, Folder 49)
    - Review - Bob Morgan's Compiler Book (Box 22, Folder 50)
    - LANL Forms - 1991 Clearance (Box 22, Folder 51)
    - PLDI Reviews (Kathryn McKinley) (Box 22, Folder 52)
    - HUG Special Issue vol. 14, Issues 6 and 7 (Box 22, Folder 53)
    - Telescoping Languages IEEE Proceedings. October 2004 (Box 22, Folder 54)
    - DARPA HPCS (Box 22, Folder 55)
    - HPCS Principal Investigator Meeting. 29 Oct - 1 Nov 2002. Scottsdale, AZ (Box 22, Folder 56)
    - HPCS DAPRA Kick off. 16-17 Sept 2002 (Box 22, Folder 57)
    - DARPA HPC Teleconferences (Box 22, Folder 58)
    - Review of Grant # 82138S07-1 "Advanced Static and Dynamic Scheduling…" (Box 22, Folder 59)
    - IEEE Proceedings - Telescoping Languages Paper. October 2004 (Box 22, Folder 60)
    - Journal of Grid Computing 2002 (Box 22, Folder 61)
    - IEEE/TP DPS # 116424 July 2002 (Box 22, Folder 62)
    - TPDS # 116424 September 2002 (Box 22, Folder 63)
    - IEEE Proceedings 2003 (Box 22, Folder 64)
    - IEEE Special Issue Proposal. 15 May 2002 (Box 22, Folder 65)
    - IEEE - TPDPS # 116424 - 1 for Review 2003 (Box 22, Folder 66)
    - IEEE - TPDPS # 116424 for Review 2003 (Box 22, Folder 67)
    - Future Generations Computer Systems Ed. Board Member 2004 (Box 22, Folder 68)
    - Future Generation Computer Systems Journal - Ed. Board Appt. 2004 (Box 22, Folder 69)
    - Invited Reviewer (IEEE) 2004 (Box 22, Folder 70)
    - JOGC Paper Review 2003 (Box 22, Folder 71)
    - Mid-Year DCI EAB Update Teleconference. 23 July 2001 (Box 22, Folder 72)
    - DARPA HPCS-PI Contact List E-mail Addresses. Nov 2002 (Box 22, Folder 73)
    - DARPA HPCS - Godiva SW Group E-mail Addresses. Sept 2002 (Box 22, Folder 74)
    - HP/Godiva Friday Teleconference (Box 22, Folder 75)
    - IBM Deep Computing Institute EA Board Mtg. 30 Nov - 1 Dec 1999 (Box 22, Folder 76)
    - Los Alamos National Laboratory Science and Technology Assessment 1 July 2001 - 30 June 2002 (Box 22, Folder 77)
    - Senate (Budget) Letters (Box 22, Folder 78)
    - LANL Donirm Super Computer. 24-25 Aug 1989 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Argonne Parallel Computing Seminar. 7-8 Sept 1989 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Control Data. 3-4 May 1989 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - SIAM - Tucson, AA. 20-22 March 1989 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Hopcroft Report (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Opportunities Report (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Perkin-Elmer System (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Shell Faculty Forum Guests (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - LASL Agreement (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - The Dana Group (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - DATAFLOW Correspondence (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - DATAFLOW Stock Info (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - DATAFLOW Business Plan (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - DANA Tech Reports (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Dungworth (CRAY). 16 Sept 1992 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - CRAY (General) (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - DANA (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - DANA Shareholder Info (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - CRAY Mtg. 10 March 1993 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Capital One Consulting 1999 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - CRAY Correspondence (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - CODESMITH Common Stock (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - CODESMITH Board Meetings (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - NY Doctoral Program Univ. of Rochester. 11-12 Oct 1990. (1 of 2) (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - NY Doctoral Program Univ. of Rochester. 11-12 Oct 1990. (2 of 2) (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - NY Doctoral Program Site Visit Review November 1990 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - State Board of Education Rating Committee - NY Region 1989 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - U.S. Department of Commerce (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Livermore Labs Contract (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Final Intergraph Contract (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - HVP July 1 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Spectracell Labs (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - A Review of Stanford's Center for Integrated Turbulence Simulations (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - CRAY Computer Engineering Award (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - ASCI-ASAP Center Review Guidelines. 28-29 Oct 1998 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - U of H (University of Houston) (1 of 3) (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - U of H (University of Houston) (2 of 3) (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - U of H (University of Houston) (3 of 3) (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Texas Agreement. 20 Sept 1990 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - NCMI Advisory Committee (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Georgia Tech Info (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Georgia Tech Advisory Board (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Pantex Groundwater Study 1990 (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - UT CS Advisory Committee (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - University of Houston Faculty Search 2002 (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - NPACI Program Plan 2000 (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - NCSA (Box 23, Folder 47)
    - National Computational Science Alliance. 1 Oct 1998 - 30 Sept 1999 (Box 23, Folder 48)
    - Development Meeting with Garrett Dolan 2006 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Climate Survey (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Research Accounting at Rice/Herron Report (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Database - Ken Kennedy (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - U of H Chair Search (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - U of H Chair Search 2003 - Candidates to Invite (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Other U of H Committees (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - U of H Gear Program Review. April 2004 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - UH Newsletters (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - State Infrastructures Protection Advisory Committee (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - CISE (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Proposal for DoD Modernization. 31 May 1995. (1 of 3) (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Proposal for DoD Modernization. 31 May 1995. (2 of 3) (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Proposal for DoD Modernization. 31 May 1995. (3 of 3) (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Defense Modernization (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - ARL Technical Assessment Board Background Materials. March 1996 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - DARPA ITO General PI Mtg. (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - National Information Infrastructure (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - NII Report (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - CSTB (White House) (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Advanced Visual Systems Inc. (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - ACM/SICPLAN Interview (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - ACM Fellow (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - AAAS (American Association for the Advancement of Science) (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - National Research Council (NRC) (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - NRC Mailing Lists (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - LANL Search - 2001 Resumes (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Army Research Lab (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Directorate for Computer and Information Science and Engineering Advisory Committee Mtg. 5-6 June 1993. (1 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Directorate for Computer and Information Science and Engineering Advisory Committee Mtg. 5-6 June 1993. (2 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Paul Woodward Comments on HPF (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - UH EM Code Mtg. (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - NHSE 30 Sept 1997 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - UH CS Dept. Chair Search Meeting. 14 Feb 2003 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - UH CS Department Head Search (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Seymour Cray Award (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - DCI EAB 2002 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Society for the Performing Arts (SPA) 1987-1996 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - SPA Marketing Committee (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - NSF Workshop on Planning for Growth of Academic Computer Science (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Report - NY Site Visit (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - University of Rochester (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Originals (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Faculty/General (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - New Curriculum (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - University of Rochester Visits (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Administration CE Relation (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Funding (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Research/Slides (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Courses (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Students/Recruiting (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - University of Rochester Computer Science (1 of 2) (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - University of Rochester Computer Science (2 of 2) (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - AccessWare Inc. Financial Package. January 1995 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - AccessWare Board of Directors (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - AccessWare HUP - Board of Directors (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - AccessWare Board Meeting 4 August 1995 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - AccessWare Inc. Business Plan and other printed materials (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - AccessWare Business Plan March 1997 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - AccessWare Business Plan/Strategy (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - UH COSC Chair Search 2002 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - U of H Chair Search 2003 Possible Candidates (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - U of H Chair Search 2003 Rejections (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - NAE 2005 Officers Election (Ballot) (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - NAE Member Comments - 2006 Election (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - National Light Rail Project Nomination for Funding 2003 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Adv. Committee on Cyber Infrastructure Testimony. 22 Jan 2002 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - HPCC Advisory Committee (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - SC-COSMIC Joint Conference, 25-28 June 1998 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - White House Advisory Committee (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - White House (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Rice Minority Programs (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - From Red Tape to Results - Al Gore (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Office of Under Secretary of Defense (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - PITAC National Security Panel (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - PITAC Meeting in Houston (cancelled) November 2001 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - PITAC NSP - Teleconference 2001 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - PITAC Teleconference 3 Aug 2001 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - PITAC Renewal Letter to TX Senators (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - NSA Technology Forecast (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - DCI EAB Meeting Logistics 2000 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - NAE References 2006 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - IEEE Fellows Ref Forms (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - SPA Meetings (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - CPSMA Security (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - HPCC Workshop List (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - National Research Council (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - ARMY (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Military Critical Data Agreement 2003 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - UH American Express Card (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - RENCI National Advisory Council 2007 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Grid Republic Teleconference (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Teleconference with Harvard Hill. 28 Feb 2002 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Rice-Baylor Joint Programs Committee (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Academy of Medicine, Eng., and Sci. Meeting. 5-6 Jan 2006 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - NSF SBIR Phase II Review Oct 2003 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - CERCS - Georgia Institute of Technology (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - JOGC Review December 2002 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Paper for Review (Anirban) C777: Distributed Computing (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - HPCC Workshop (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - HPCC Workshop. 12 June 1995 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Gordon Bell Awards (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Comments regarding CISE Support of Science (PITAC paper by Ed Lazowska) (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Europar Review - Anirban reviews "Grid and Cluster Computing" (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Envirotechnologies Systems, Inc. and Agritec, Inc. 2001 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - JCST 0509-1644 (paper for review) (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Science Foundation Ireland Proposal Review January 2005 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Journal of Parallel and Distributed Computing. 5 April 2005 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Science Foundation Ireland: Parallel Computing on Heterogeneous Clusters - Review due end of Dec 2001 (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - ICS '02 Referee Assignments (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - IEEE (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - SPA (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - SPA Marketing Plan 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (fellow nomination) (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences 2005 Induction and New Member Packets (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - AAAS Website (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - AAAS Information 2005 (Box 26, Folder 48)
    - AAAS Acceptance 2005 (Box 26, Folder 49)
    - Tera Computer Company Board of Directors Meeting. 27 Oct 1994 (Box 26, Folder 50)
    - Tera Computer Company Board of Directors Meeting. 16 Nov 1993 (Box 26, Folder 51)
    - Tera Computer Company 1995 (Box 26, Folder 52)
    - PITAC Thank You Letter 2007 (Box 26, Folder 53)
    - Horizon Manual (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - The Portland Group (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Tera Computer Company Board of Directors Meeting. 14 Feb 1992 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Tera Computer Company Board of Directors Meeting. 4 Aug 1992 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Tera Computer Company Board of Directors Meeting. 27 April 1993 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Tera Computer Company Board of Directors Meeting. 20 April 1994 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Tera Computer Company Board of Directors Meeting. 7 Feb 1996 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Tera Computer Company Board of Directors Meeting. 11 June 1996 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Tera Computer Company Board of Directors Meeting. 7 Aug 1996 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Tera Computer Company Board of Directors Meeting. 19 Feb 1997 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Tera Computer Company Board of Directors Meeting. 20 March 1997 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Tera Computer Company Board of Directors Meeting. 5 Feb 1998 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Tera Computer Company Board of Directors Meeting. 5 Aug 1998 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Tera Computer Company Board of Directors Meeting. 4 Nov 1998 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Tera Computer Company Board of Directors Meeting. 3 Nov 1999 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Tera Computer Company Board of Directors Meeting. 2 Feb 2000 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Tera Computer Company 1995 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Tera Computer Company 1996 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Tera Computer Company 1995 Stock Option Plan (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Tera Computer Company Shareholder Info. 25 April 1995 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Tera Shareholder Info 1998 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Tera Stock Agreements 1998 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Tera Computer Company 1997 Press release and 1998 Registration statement (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Tera Computer Company Documents 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Corky's Digital Proposal (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Tera Computer Presentation (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Tera Computer Company Stock/Disclosure (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Tera Computer Company Documents to be signed (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Tera/Cray board meeting 2000 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Aerospace Engineering - There are no Exceptionally Well Qualified Foreign… (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Aerospace Engineering - Quota and At-Large Candidates (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Bioengineering - Exceptionally Well Qualified Foreign Associate Candidates (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Bioengineering - Quota and At-Large Candidates (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Chemical Engineering - Exceptionally Well Qualified Foreign Associate Candidates (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Chemical Engineering - Quota and At-Large Candidates (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Civil Engineering - Exceptionally Well Qualified Foreign Associate Candidates (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Civil Engineering - Quota and At-Large Candidates (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Computer Science - Exceptionally Well Qualified Foreign Associate Candidates (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Computer Science - Quota and At-Large Candidates (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Electric Power/Energy Systems Engineering - Exceptionally Well Qualified Foreign Associate Candidates (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Electric Power/Energy Systems Engineering - Quota and At-Large Candidates (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Electronics Engineering - Exceptionally Well Qualified, Quota, and At-Large Candidates (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Industrial, Manufacturing, and Operational Systems Engineering - Exceptionally Well Qualified, Quota, and At-Large Candidates (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Materials Engineering - Exceptionally Well Qualified, Quota, and At-Large Candidates (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Mechanical Engineering - Exceptionally Well Qualified, Quota, and At-Large Candidates (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Petroleum, Mining, and Geological Engineering - Exceptionally Well Qualified, Quota, and At-Large Candidates (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Special Fields and Interdisciplinary Engineering - Exceptionally Well Qualified, Quota, and At-Large Candidates (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - NAE 1999 Election Committee on Membership Meeting Agenda. 5 Dec 1998 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - NAE Computer Science and Engineering Peer Committee. 7 Oct 1994 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - NAE Computer Science and Engineering Peer Committee. 29 Sept 1995 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - NAE Committee on Membership Meeting Agenda. 4 Dec 1995 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - NAE 33rd Election Peer Committee Workshop. 24 Jan 1995 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - "Human Capital: Specialized Workforce Needs for an Information Economy" Draft (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - BMS Review of Core Mathematics Activities (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - National Research Council Appointments (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Report of SSB/ASEB Visiting Committee (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - May 1996 Current Events (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - June 3 Meeting of Advisory Council (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Mathematical Research in Cosmology (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Record Linkage Workshop (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Monte Carlo Simulation in Virtual Experiments (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Electromet. Techniques for DOE Spent Fuel Treatment (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - National Research Council Nominating Members (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - NRC Nominating Members of Various Boards 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - NRC Meeting 13-14 Oct 1995 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - NRC Draft: 1996 Action Plan (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - NRC Report to Congress 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - NRC New Member Information (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - NRC re: Harold Liebowitz 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - NRC New Member Nominations. 4 April 1996 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - NRC Workshop III: HPCC Research and Application Needs. 24 Aug 1995 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - NRC Computer Science and Telecommunications Board. 21-22 Jan 1993 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - NRC Computer Science and Telecommunications Board. 13-14 Sept 1993 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - NRC Computer Science and Telecommunications Board. 10-11 Jan 1994 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - NRC Commission on Physical Sciences, Mathematics, and Applications Retreat Book. 23-24 Feb 1996 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - NRC Commission on Physical Sciences, Mathematics, and Applications Commission Business Materials. 23-24 Feb 1996 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - NRC Commission on Physical Sciences, Mathematics, and Applications Commission Meeting. 28-29 June 1996 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - NRC Commission on Physical Sciences, Mathematics, and Applications. 18-19 Oct 1996. (1 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - NRC Commission on Physical Sciences, Mathematics, and Applications. 18-19 Oct 1996 (2 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - NRC Board Reports. 13-14 Oct 1995 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - NRC Computer Science and Telecommunications Board. 24-25 May 1993 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - NRC A Strategic Forum on Rights and Responsibilities for Participants in Networked Communities. 18-19 Feb 1993 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - NRC/CSTB Review Future of Supercomputing (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Telecom Opportunity Institute (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Chase.com TTOI Curriculum (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - TTOI Board Materials 2002 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - TTOI Board Meeting. 14 June 2002 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - The Telecom Opportunity Institute Board Meetings 2003 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - TTOI Board Meeting. 10 Dec 2003 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - TTOI Youth Curriculum Format 2001 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Advisory Committee on Cyberinfrastructure (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Advanced Reality Non-disclosure agreement 2001 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Advanced Reality 2001 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Advanced Reality Documents 2002 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Baylor HGSC Visit (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - BioHouston Task Force Kick off Mtg. 31 Aug 2004 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Catalytic Compilers Executive Summary 2002 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Catalytic Compilers Advisory Board Agreement and Stock Option Agreement. 2002 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Catalytic, Inc. 2004 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - CRAY Correspondence Received/Sent. 2000-2002 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - CRAY, Inc. Review of 2002 Business Plan. 2002 February 14 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - CRAY, Inc. 2000 Annual Report (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - CRAY: The Supercomputer Company, 2004 Annual Report (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - CRAY 2005 Annual Report (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Seymour Cray Computer Engineering Award - 1999 Nomination (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - The Cascade High Productivity Language. CRAY, Inc. 2004 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - CRAY Miscellaneous Documents for Signature. 2004-2006 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - CRAY Consent Form Correspondence. 2005 June 6 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - CRAY Special HPCS Phase III Solicitation Nondisclosure Agreement. 2006 March 30 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - CRAY Nonqualified Stock Option Agreement under the 1999 Stock Option Plan of CRAY, Inc. 2002 May 29 (Box 30, Folder 4)